Fall in love with your work
Jiro Dreams of Sushi is a documentary film directed by David Gelb.
Revered sushi chef Jiro Ono strives for perfection in his work, while his eldest
son, Yoshikazu, has trouble living up to his father's legacy.
Self, played by Jiro Ono.
Self, played by Masuhiro Yamamoto.
Self, played by Yoshikazu Ono.
Self, played by Takashi Ono.
Self, played by Daisuke Nakazama.
Self, played by Hachiro Mizutani.
Jiro Dreams of Sushi is a 2011 Japanese-language American
documentary film directed by David Gelb.
The film follows Jiro Ono (小野 二郎, Ono Jirō), a then-85-year-old sushi master and
owner of Sukiyabashi Jiro, then a Michelin three-star restaurant.
Sukiyabashi Jiro is a 10-seat, sushi-only restaurant
located in a Tokyo subway station.
As of 2026, Jiro Ono serves a tasting menu of roughly 20
courses, for a minimum of JP¥88,000 (US$557).
The film also profiles Jiro's two sons, both of whom are also sushi chefs.
The younger son, Takashi (隆士), left Sukiyabashi Jiro to open a mirror
image of his father's restaurant in Roppongi Hills.
The 50-year-old elder son, Yoshikazu (禎一), obliged to succeed his father, still works for Jiro
and is faced with the prospect of one day taking over the flagship restaurant.
The film explores themes of japan, restaurant, sushi
restaurant, apprentice, based on true story.